<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DenverRocksV2</string>
    <string name="transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="history">Historical</string>
    <string name="fun">Fun</string>
    <string name="resturant">Resturants</string>


        <!---Fun Description Long Text-->

        <string name="union_station_description">Denvers Union Station is a two for one: its a working public transit station
        and a highly praised dining and shopping center.
        The station was a huge success when it first opened to the public in 1881,
        providing railroad service until the center of the building caught fire in 1894.
        </string>

        <string name="denver_art_museum">With galleries showcasing more than 70,000 works by famed artists such as
        Vincent Van Gogh and Winslow Homer, the Denver Art Museum houses one of the most impressive collections
        of art between Chicago and the West Coast. Spread across two buildings, the museums holdings range from
        pre-Columbian artifacts to contemporary displays</string>

        <string name="red_rocks">With its excellent views of the Rocky Mountains, miles of hiking trails and cinnamon-hued
        sandstone cliffs, Red Rocks Park is a big draw for outdoors enthusiasts. Occupying 700-some acres, this impressive
        park offers visitors the opportunity to experience the fascinating geographic transition between the Great Plains
        and the Rocky Mountains. </string>

        <string name="larimer_square">In 1858, a group of American Indians and settlers struck gold at the foot of the Rocky Mountains.
        Their discovery soon spread back to the East Coast, prompting people to pick up and move west. The site of the original pioneer
        camp (known back then as Auraria) soon grew into the charming area now known as Larimer Square. </string>

        <string name="denver_botantic_gardens">The Denver Botanic Gardens 24 acres feature a whopping 50 gardens for visitors to explore.
        This expansive facility in downtown Denvers Cheesman Park treats travelers to a variety of different environments, from a traditional
        Japanese garden (complete with bonsai trees) to the South African Plaza blooming with exotic plants like asparagus fern and torch lilies.
        </string>

        <string name="Museum_of_Nature">With exhibits featuring everything from dinosaur bones to Egyptian mummies, the Denver Museum of Nature and
        Science inspires learning in the young and young at heart. This impressive facility houses artifacts pertaining to a variety of scientific
        areas, including anthropology, zoology, geology, health sciences, paleontology and space science. </string>

        <string name="coors_field">Named for Denvers famed beer, Coors Field in Denvers LoDo district is home to Major League Baseballs
        Colorado Rockies. The stadium occupies a whopping 76 acres and has the capacity for more than 50,000 people. Of course, the main
        reason to come to Coors Field is to catch a game, but there is more to this stadium than a diamond. </string>

        <!---Historical Description Long Text-->

        <string name="bent_fort">Bent’s Old Fort National Historic Site features a reconstruction of the 1840s trading post that was an important point
        for fur trade on the Santa Fe Trail.  When you visit, take a tour and watch a living history demonstration about fur trade and life at Bent’s Old Fort.</string>

        <string name="national_monument">Colorado National Monument preserves amazing sandstone towers and canyons, and desert ecosystems. When you visit, drive
        or bike along Rim Rock Drive and stop for a snack at one of the scenic picnic areas.</string>

        <string name="curecanti">The three reservoirs of the Curecanti National Recreation Area are great places for boating, fishing, hiking, camping, and
        bird watching.  When you visit, take a boat tour with a ranger on Morrow Point Reservoir and learn about the geology, wildlife and history of the Gunnison River.</string>

        <string name="dinosaur">Dinosaur National Monument preserves fossils, petroglyphs, and canyon ecosystems.
When you visit, stop at the Carnegie Dinosaur Quarry, and see nearly 1500 fossilized bones from Allosaurus,
        Apatosaurus, Stegosaurus, and other dinosaurs.</string>

        <string name="florissant">Florissant Fossil Beds National Monument protects 34 million-year-old fossils of redwood trees and insects.
        When you visit, take a hike through a petrified forest and enjoy views of Pikes Peak.</string>

        <string name="hovenweep">Hovenweep National Monument includes six prehistoric villages built by Ancestral Puebloan people
        nearly 800 years ago.  When you visit, take a short hike over mesa tops and through sagebrush to see ancient structures,
        including a three-story tower and kivas.</string>

        <string name="sandcreek">Sand Creek Massacre National Historic Site commemorates the events of November 29, 1864,
        when Colorado volunteer soldiers attacked an encampment of over 500 Cheyenne and Arapaho people. The site was established
        to preserve and protect the cultural landscape of the massacre, enhance public understanding, and minimize similar incidents in the future.
When you visit, learn about the Massacre from an interpretive ranger (daily at 10 am and 2 pm).</string>

        <string name="yuccahouse">Yucca House National Monument preserves the remains of an 600-room Ancestral Pueblo village, and one of the largest
        archaeological sites in Colorado.  When you visit, take a short walk through a desert shrubland, see the remains of the Upper House and the
        Lower House, and look for the spring that provided water for the people who lived here.</string>


        <!---Resturant Description Long Text-->

        <string name="maria_empanada">Maria Empanada basically does one thingbrilliantly. What it does is authentic Argentinian empanadas in a variety of
        forms, from savory to sweet. In spite of its location on a busy corner of South Broadway, its an oasis of deliciousness.</string>

        <string name="maria_address">1298 S. Broadway, Denver, CO 80210</string>

        <string name="acron">Located in The Source, the former foundry building turned chic multi-venue marketplace on Brighton Boulevard in RiNo, Acorn
        features an aptly industrial-chic aesthetic with its exposed bricks and pipes. The restaurant is the offshoot of tasty.</string>

        <string name="acron_address">3350 Brighton Blvd, Denver, CO 80216</string>

        <string name="oldmajor">The focus at this Highlands-area eatery is on heritage-raised meats from Colorado farms. The restaurant does its own butchering
        and cures the meats in-house (you can see the charcuterie room from the dining area). While the emphasis is on awesome</string>

        <string name="oldmajor_address">3316 Tejon St, Denver, CO 80211</string>

        <string name="olive">Olive and Finch features made from scratch and made to order three meals a day. Breads are baked daily, sauces are house-made,
        juices are pressed on site and the restaurants chefs cure and smoke the meats. Like the original Uptown location this place is great</string>

        <string name="olive_address">3390 1st Avenue, Denver, CO 80206</string>

        <string name="work">As its name suggests, Work and Class, which opened in 2014, is down to earth and deliberately reflective of the owners own
        working-class roots. The exceptional food, however, makes it in any class. Red-chile braised pork and coriander-roasted...  Read More</string>

        <string name="work_address">2500 Larimer St, Denver, CO 80205</string>

        <string name="ilposto">Il Posto moved from its cramped Uptown location to an airy, contemporary space in Denvers newest trending culinary neighborhood,
        RiNo. Trendy, however, is not what owner-chef Andrea Frizzi is going for. Il Posto's menu emphasizes simple, fresh, and simple tastes.</string>

        <string name="ilposto_address">2601 Larimer Street, Denver, CO 80205</string>

        <string name="bistro">Tucked into a secluded breezeway off Larimer Square, intimate Bistro Vendome captures the essence of a Parisian bistro in its
        ambience and menu. Expect French classics (some rotating) such as cassoulet, duck confit, escargot, steak au poivre and other great dishes.</string>

        <string name="bistro_address">1420 Larimer St, Denver, CO 80202</string>

        <string name="hopalley">Located in the northern reaches of Denvers River North (RiNo) neighborhood, where many of the citys newest restaurants
        are taking root, Hop Alley is the second venue from Tommy Lee and sister restaurant to Lees successful Uncle in the best.</string>

        <string name="hopalley_address">3500 Larimer Street, Denver, CO 80205</string>

        <string name="fruiton">Chef Alex Seidel opened Fruition Restaurant in 2007. With its seasonally driven menu of upscale comfort food and a
        well-curated wine list, it was an instant success. While the ubiquitous term "farm-to-table" is now overused, Seidel set the bar.</string>

        <string name="fruiton_address">1313 E. 6th Avenue, Denver, CO 80218</string>

        <string name="guardgrace">The bone-in ribeye will vie for the best steak youve ever had. Opened since 2014, Guard and Grace puts steaks
        front and center in this 9,000-square-foot modern space, but the menu showcases wood-fired options of all kinds, including veggies and sides.</string>

        <string name="guardgrace_address">1801 California St, Denver, CO 80202</string>


    </resources>

